suki wo zebune HAGUshitai
“好き”を全部ね ハグしたい
I want to hug everything that I like (I want to hug)
(dakishimetai)
(抱きしめたい)
fukuramu HAATO de GYU tto ne
膨らむハートで ギュッとね
An expanding heart makes it kind of tight (quite a sight)
(meippai ne)
(目一杯ね)
DOKI DOKI hassei tahatsu
ドキドキ発生多発
Excitement breaks out multiple times (here comes trouble)
(jiken boppatsu)
(事件勃発)
kaisatsu de shingou de koumon de
改札で 信号で 校門で
At the ticket barrier, the traffic lights, the school gate (anywhere)
(ANYWHERE)
tsukisusunjatte in janai
突き進んじゃって いんじゃない
Taking the plunge should be fine, wouldn't it (Not at all it wouldn't)
(zenzen injanai)
(全然いんじゃない)
hazunda HIPPU no NORI de ne
弾んだヒップのノリでね
Expanded hips makes it easy to put on (it's kind of fun)
(tanoshiku ne)
(楽しくね)
WAKUWAKU kasoku YABAI
ワクワク加速ヤバい
Nervously accelerate, oh great (seriously won't stop)
(maji tomannai)
(まじ止まんない)
haretemo âme demo OUR MORNING'S BRIGHTENING
晴れても雨でも Our Morning's Brightening!!
If it's sun or if it's rain, Our Morning's Brightening!!
A B C D E F G ja hakarenai seifuku no uchigawa
A・B・C・D・E・F・G じゃ測れない 制服の内側
A.B.C.D.E.F.G you can't measure it! Inside of the uniform something is
shikachuu da shi SAIZU kawaru yume yosoku wa fukanou
進化中だし サイズ変わる夢 予測は不可能
Evolving size, changing dream, you can't predict it...!
kyoumi ni riyuu wa nai yo ne
興味に理由はないよね？
There's no interest in reason, right? (Plain and simple)
(tanjunmeikai)
(単純明快)
ki ni naru koto ga ki ni narimasu
気になることが 気になります
You'll get worried over worries
tokenai suushiki to DEREnai
解けない数式とデレない
Don't trouble yourself with an unsolvable formula (tiringly tough tiringly tough)
(nankaikonpai)
(なんかいこんぱい)
ano ko wa tsune ni ne onaji omo sa
あのコは常にね 同じ重要さ
With that girl it's always the same (mainly)
shigyou no chaimu ga RISETTO SAIN
始業のチャイムがリセットサイン
It's a sign the starting bell has reset
kinou no shittai wa shoukyo de iku yo
昨日の失態は消去でいくよ
Yesterday's mistakes are being cleared, here we go!
DERIKEETO de DAINAMIKKU LOW TEENAGERS
デリケートでダイナミック Low Teenagers
Delicate and dynamic Low Teenagers
FURIRU de kakushita honne naze oshieaitai
フリルで隠した本音 なぜ教え合いたい…！？
Frilled, hidden motive- why do you want to join them together... !?
suki ni zenbu ne TACCHI shitai
“好き”に全部ね タッチしたい
I want to touch everything that I like (I want to be sure)
(tashikametai)
(確かめたい)
tokimeku HAATO de sotto ne
ときめくハートで そっとね
My heart's fluttering, treat it softly (gently)
(yasashiku ne)
(優しくね)
KIRAKIRA hasshin funpatsu
キラキラ発信奮発
Sparkling splurge of submissions (experiments one after the other)
(jiken renpatsu)
(実験連発)
kyoushitsu de rouka de bukatsu de
教室で 廊下で 部活で
In the class, the halls, club activities (anywhere)
(ANYWHERE)
tsukisusunjatte in janai
突き進んじゃって いんじゃない
Taking the plunge should be fine, wouldn't it (Not at all it wouldn't)
(zenzen injanai)
(全然いんじゃない)
shirigomi HIPPU mo hoppu NI
尻込みヒップもホップに
Hesitant hip and a hesitant hop (lively now)
(genki ni ne)
(元気にね)
FURUFURU yuuki wo dashi
フルフル勇気を出し
Bring out all your bravery (bring out that spirit)
(sono ki wo dashi)
(その気を出し)
mukae teki nashi mayou hima nashi manande asonde
向かえ敵なし 迷う暇なし 学んで遊んで
Without opposition, without losing time, in study and play,
WE MUST CHOOSE BRIGHT THINGS